<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Movie and TV Shows</string>
    <string name="title_movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="title_tv_shows">TV Shows</string>

    <string-array name="movie_title">
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>The Mule</item>
        <item>Bird Box </item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_youtube_id">
        <item>xLCn88bfW1o</item>
        <item>zwPn9ZnbCo0</item>
        <item>N_QksSzK7sI</item>
        <item>MPWMBITCudM</item>
        <item>mP0VHJYFOAU</item>
        <item>lcwmDAYt22k</item>
        <item>ovFpFtZ2Tvk</item>
        <item>IRsFc2gguEg</item>
        <item>95ghQs5AmNk</item>
        <item>QAhcDHRZOak</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_release">
        <item>September 28, 2018</item>
        <item>November 20, 2018</item>
        <item>December 14, 2018</item>
        <item>December 13, 2018</item>
        <item>October 24, 2018</item>
        <item>December 15, 2018</item>
        <item>November 21, 2018</item>
        <item>November 27, 2018</item>
        <item>January 16, 2019</item>
        <item>October 19, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_desc">
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
        <item>A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.</item>
        <item>Earl Stone, a man in his 80s, is broke, alone, and facing foreclosure of his business when he is offered a job that simply requires him to drive. Easy enough, but, unbeknownst to Earl, he’s just signed on as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. He does so well that his cargo increases exponentially, and Earl hit the radar of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates.</item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his family\'s past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.</item>
        <item>Many thousands of years in the future, Earth’s cities roam the globe on huge wheels, devouring each other in a struggle for ever diminishing resources. On one of these massive traction cities, the old London, Tom Natsworthy has an unexpected encounter with a mysterious young woman from the wastelands who will change the course of his life forever.</item>
        <item>In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.</item>
        <item>Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d\'état is taking place in Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="movie_bg">
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_themule</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mortalengine</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
    </array>


    <string-array name="tvshow_title">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippunden</item>
        <item>The Simpson</item>
        <item>The Umbrella Academy</item>
        <item>Shameless</item>
        <item>NCIS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tvshow_youtube_id">
        <item>D5J9h0HPklE</item>
        <item>6tTM9nbRk5A</item>
        <item>wuIbeQv3v7c</item>
        <item>4KSN7mxhiYE</item>
        <item>wwoq3o_yNMw</item>
        <item>thh7bVCgDHs</item>
        <item>HRV6tMR-SSs</item>
        <item>0DAmWHxeoKw</item>
        <item>ex95FSZOT04</item>
        <item>BhtDgn31XZo</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="tvshow_bg">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_simpson</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_umbrella</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_shameless</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
    </array>


    <string-array name="tvshow_score">
        <item>50%</item>
        <item>61%</item>
        <item>71%</item>
        <item>64%</item>
        <item>65%</item>
        <item>75%</item>
        <item>71%</item>
        <item>77%</item>
        <item>78%</item>
        <item>67%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tvshow_release">
        <item>October 10, 2012</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>February 26, 1986</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>February 15, 2007</item>
        <item>December 17, 1989</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>January 9, 2011</item>
        <item>September 23, 2003</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tvshow_desc">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.</item>
        <item>The Doom Patrol’s members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman abilities — but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden, the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate the weirdest phenomena in existence — and to protect Earth from what they find.</item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the dragon balls brought her to Goku's home. Together, they set off to find all seven dragon balls in an adventure.</item>
        <item>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn't just any ordinary kid, he's a member of one of the world's most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.</item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin' Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he's not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.</item>
        <item>Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.</item>
        <item>A dysfunctional family of superheroes comes together to solve the mystery of their father's death, the threat of the apocalypse and more.</item>
        <item>Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious, independent kids, who without him would be... perhaps better off. When Frank's not at the bar spending what little money they have, he's passed out on the floor. But the kids have found ways to grow up in spite of him. They may not be like any family you know, but they make no apologies for being exactly who they are.</item>
        <item>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
